do you ever what I'm hearing I Hoshi and
they said XX brother two sisters and the
prospect of philly my dad she makes a
sure I wasn't going to do this and
America will hang ah she listened she's
the first one to listen to what you
wanted I just messing up so much they
came from a collab the only a cloud
computing echo island is the largest
island Ohio which is the southern island
nation but accola is a large silent on
my office all of it he said island was
the island off the coast of battle
he would have a comfortable as panel
tonight for physical reasons first off
this is steep now I read about these
people in the news and I see one on the
news and i will remove him for a while
oh just this whole house reflects the
greatest of the city and people who give
up himself by follows the construction
work he came in from around like things
rhyme too addicted he probably the
mid-fifties he was looking for
opportunity and the opportunity wasn't
as neighbor see now a desk or you know
shoot I job or he was looking for a job
lovely is the folks here to take him in
some community to welcome him and a kid
with loving arms that opened on and he
got a job as a construction worker happy
group with gas copy for a little bit
then he got the 310 job local retail
labors and that's what he did but his
life was a testament that you know you
don't have to be a mover a shaker like
that not us I don't you sure they did
what they did because what do I thing to
do it wasn't their job and do the things
they did for their communities and and
their employees their people almost
think any of us can do that and held on
that's what before my father was about
that was his example to us going up as
soon as the need you better take my
temple I'll never forget those young man
hurt on him Ruth Martin and it was
robbed and said and you lost them you
know sure hindle Kashmir anything that
is sup- income and they say my father
his friends mom to put the other benefit
to raise some money talk his manface
bill
and some of our areas from tonight as
you got ipod tonight you don't just
induct him if there was a building or
the pillar national fame he be staying
holy home Todd
his adversities volunteerism none that
were impossible up my mother at home
raising my kids and me without my floors
countess counting like talking to people
they can phone calls time to raise money
trying to to get social supply here for
that fit before he did several
fundraisers for uh he said I've got the
hundred hawker centre he did several
deaf test for college ahmad al who serve
the central community here at Cleveland
and all heals over there oh he was just
trying with me simple 5-asa need all of
the conf I days which is the description
of a prototypical con man I'm just me
just do what I do so we all have to
thank my mother for being there all the
time oh he was just always willing to
help and I also want to thank deputy Dan
Hanson and the rest of the people who
work with them for this dis event I mean
this is Cleveland look around you CLE
let this enough
are you know the melting pot that didn't
melt because you should we matter when
we came from Oz and my Irish heritage
didn't teach me to be Irish you taught
me before she ain't like I heard him
talk about how his parents were from
Poland or whoever they were immigrants
three that was the commonality his
narrow kiss too wow talk about you know
find out what their experience was this
is a great thing I'm going on to my
ethnic oddly because it wasn't just the
outfit the borders were not hard fat
borders it was a great lesson a great
way to promote I'm so proud that I'm an
Irishman and I was raised by the large
me because basically appreciate
everybody else's heritage and where they
came from and I am I here it's time for
that and the Empire's community here in
Cleveland so ah Cleveland I be very
proud this gathering people out of the
city we've got good we've got a great
great city here I did love this city you
really did he'd be very pleased with
this tonight can be very humble I'm very
thankful end up come on that grew all
mine thank you so much